[{"question": "What is the price of the New Xpax?", "choices": ["RM 5", "RM 10", "RM 20"], "answer": 1}, {"question": "Which one is not the benefit of the New Xpax?", "choices": ["free 10GB hi-speed Facebook Internet", "free 10GB Instagram", "preload with RM6 credit"], "answer": 1}, {"question": "What is the call rate of Xpax?", "choices": ["30 sen/min", "25 sen/min", "35 sen/min"], "answer": 0}, {"question": "What is the SMS rate of Xpax", "choices": ["20 sen/sms", "30 sen/sms", "15 sen/sms"], "answer": 2}, {"question": "What is the MMS rate of Xpax?", "choices": ["55 sen/mms", "50 sen/mms", "40 sen/mms"], "answer": 1}, {"question": "How can I subscribe extra 2GB quota for Daily Internet Plans?", "choices": ["dial *118*2*1#", "dial *118*2*2#", "dial *118*2*3#"], "answer": 0}, {"question": "How can I subscribe extra 4GB quota for Daily Internet Plans?", "choices": ["dial *118*2*4#", "dial *118*2*3#", "dial *118*2*2#"], "answer": 2}, {"question": "Which one is not the partners for Video Walla?", "choices": ["iflix", "dimsum", "bbc"], "answer": 2}, {"question": "Which one is/are the partners for Music Walla?", "choices": ["hitz.fm", "joox", "all the above"], "answer": 2}, {"question": "What is the price of the Weekly Internet Plan with quota of 1.5GB?", "choices": ["RM 6", "RM 10", "RM 19"], "answer": 0}, {"question": "How to subscribe Weekly Internet Plan with 1.5GB quota?", "choices": ["dial *118*2*3#", "dial *118*3*2#", "dial *118*2*4#"], "answer": 0}, {"question": "What is the quota for Weekly Internet Plan of price RM 10?", "choices": ["6 GB", "10 GB", "15 GB"], "answer": 0}, {"question": "How can I check the usage balance of the FREE 10GB Instagram?", "choices": ["dial *118*1*1*2#", "dial *118*1*1*3#", "dial *118*1*1*4#"], "answer": 0}, {"question": "Who can subscribe to Add-On plans?", "choices": ["prepaid customer", "postpaid customer", "all customer"], "answer": 0}, {"question": "How much free quota is offered to Daily Video Walla subscription?", "choices": ["500 MB", "1 GB", "3 GB"], "answer": 1}, {"question": "Which Internet Plan offers/offer triple quota?", "choices": ["Weekly Internet Plan", "Monthly Internet Plan", "All the above"], "answer": 2}]